<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | STA 198 / GLHLTH 298</title>
    <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©2022</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/amy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/amy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Amy Herring, and my pronouns are she/her/hers. I am Sara &amp;amp; Charles Ayres Distinguished Professor in the Department of Statistical Science and also hold appointments in the Duke Global Health Institute and in the Department of Biostatistics &amp;amp; Bioinformatics. I enjoy working on a variety of research projects on campus and beyond, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to learn about your own interests! My work is focused on statistics and its applications in health, including analysis of longitudinal or otherwise correlated data, missing data and measurement error, Bayesian methods, and general biostatistics.  I earned my doctorate in biostatistics at Harvard, and before that I completed an undergraduate double major in English and mathematics. In addition to my work and family activities (data entry at swim meets, ha!), I enjoy reading, cats, &lt;a href=&#34;https://store.stonemaiergames.com/products/wingspan&#34;&gt;Wingspan&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bthreewellness.punchpass.com&#34;&gt;fitness classes led by a Duke alum&lt;/a&gt;, and working outdoors (i.e., working on laptop on my porch overlooking the garden with a cup of black tea!).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/jackie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/jackie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! My name is Jackie, and I am a second year in the Masters of Statistical Science (MSS) program. I studied Economics for my undergrad at Yale, and after graduating in 2019, I worked in the tech infrastructure department of a bank (i.e. working with developers to create applications for other developers at the bank, very meta I know). I’m interested in neuroscience, specifically in decision-making, but I’m excited to see how my interests evolve. Outside of class, I love baking &amp;amp; watching basketball (mostly the NBA but excited to watch Duke games), and I’m excited to get back into the pool after a hiatus post-collegiate swimming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/riya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/riya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! My name is Riya Mohan and I&amp;rsquo;m a rising junior at Duke. I am currently pursuing a Program II or a self-designed major titled &amp;ldquo;The Ethical and Regulatory Issues of Human Genomic Editing&amp;rdquo;. At Duke, I&amp;rsquo;m a Margolis Scholar and am a part of Ethical Tech and Duke Cyber. Outside academic settings, I love coffee, exploring, and reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sta-198-glhlth-298-fall-2022.github.io/website/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rigorous introduction to health data science using current applications in biomedical research, epidemiology, and health policy. Use modern statistical software to conduct reproducible data exploration, visualization, and analysis. Interpret and translate results for interdisciplinary researchers. Critically evaluate data-based claims, decisions, and policies. Includes exploratory data analysis, visualization, basics of probability and inference, predictive modeling and classification. This course focuses on the R computing language. No statistical or computing background is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.introds.org/&#34;&gt;centralized resource page for intro data science courses&lt;/a&gt; for great tips and help throughout the course.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
